AU DUONG TUAN

UX Designer / Developer

+84 948 935 300 hi@auduongtuan.com https://auduongtuan.com

Introduction

Overview: I am a designer x developer hybrid with good technical and design background who helps close the gap between design and development. Experienced in design systems, user interface design, and front-end development.

Background: I had got my hand in design and code since 2009 when I self-studied them to create Yahoo! 360 blog themes and WordPress websites. I hold my BFA in Design and I am getting my second bachelor's degree in Tech.

Goal: I'm looking for a product environment to help me improve my skills and learn more about product development process. Furthermore, it will be best if I can work in a <u>UX Engineer</u> role.

Experience

Aperia Vietnam

UI/UX DESIGNER/ FRONT-END DEVELOPER, FULL-TIME, APR 2020 - SEP 2022

Working as a designer/developer in design system team. My daily tasks are:

- · Create and maintain UI kits in Sketch & Figma.
- Document components (UI specs, behaviors, and <u>storybook</u>) and design patterns.
- · Handoff designs to other developers. I prototype complex concepts using HTML/CSS/JS and implement some React components.
- Also, making <u>Figma plugins</u> to help improve design workflow is my favorite task to do.

On the other hand, do some internal work such as:

- · Collaborate with Branding team to implement and maintain company website (using WordPress and Tailwind CSS)
- Create some internal tools such as Email Signature Generator, Sketch Cloud files downloader, ...

Samsung Vietnam

UI/UX DESIGNER, FULL-TIME, JAN 2020 - APR 2020

Joined in a new Samsung design team in Vietnam to build apps for IOT devices.

ECOE Vietnam

UI/UX DESIGNER, CONTRACT, MAR 2019 - OCT 2019

Joined to a design team building a new estate platform in Vietnam Market.

Viivue Web Boutique

WEB DESIGNER, PART-TIME, NOV 2018 - MAR 2019

Worked as a part-time web designer for an agency.

Yeah1 Network

GRAPHIC DESIGNER AND VIDEO EDITOR, PART-TIME, DEC 2017 - JUL 2018

Worked as a part-time designer and video editor to support marketing materials, landing pages, and videos for Phở Đặc Biệt.

PHP, WordPress

Education

University of Science (HCMUS)

BS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY, CLASS OF 2021

Keyframe Training

MOTION GRAPHIC & C4D ANIMATION, CLASS OF 2016

Skills

What I do **Design Tools** Adobe Creative Suite **Product Design** Copywriting Whimsical Design Systems Sketch, Figma, XD Motion Graphic C4D, Blender Front-end Development

University of Architecture HCMC (UAH)

BFA IN GRAPHIC DESIGN, CLASS OF 2016

Luong The Vinh High School For The Gifted

SPECIALIZATION IN PHYSICS, CLASS OF 2013

Teck Stack	Management
HTML & CSS	Jira, Notion
Javascript, Typescript	Invision, Abstract
ReactJS, NextJS	
Git	Language

Language
Vietnamese
English (IELTS 7.0)